sneak preview I think
you in the medium
term So over the
next few years we
believe that this market
could explode up to
5 trillion in notional
volume Now right now
Cal she is on
an annualized run rate
to do around 120
130 billion in notional
volume for this year
So we're talking about
a massive explosion of
where this total market
is But when you
put it the perspective
of the total derivatives
market which in 2024
was around 715 trillion
in notional volume you're
only talking about 70
basis points right that
5 trillion figure over
715 So it's a
in the compared to
where traditional derivatives sit
today And as you
point out I think
this is an expansion
of the addressable market
that derivatives don't necessarily
give you today in
terms of the risk
profile